<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Daily Challenge App</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_history_rv">HistoryActivityRV</string>
    <string name="title_activity_challenge_history">ChallengeHistoryActivity</string>
    <string name="accomplished_text">You accomplished this in:</string>
    <string name="title_history">Challenge history</string>
    <string name="challenge_0">Cooking time!;If you do not know how to cook, it\'s a good time to start. Try to learn
        a basic dish and surprise your family. If you are already an expert, learn a new recipe!</string>
    <string name="challenge_1">"Cold shower!;A cold shower every day will help you lift your mood, heal stress and help your defenses.
        It is also very good for the immune system and will leave your skin beautiful."</string>
    <string name="challenge_2">Walk for an hour;It is always a good time to start exercising.
        Walking for an hour is very healthy and will relax you. Also, it\'s a good time to think about yourself.</string>
    <string name="challenge_3">New book;If you are not currently reading any books, it\'s a good time to start.
        Take a tour of your nearest bookstore and choose the one you like the most. If on the contrary you are already reading, continue like this, you are on the right track!</string>
    <string name="challenge_4">Disconnected;Try to spend a day (or at least a few hours) without using the social networks to which we are so attached. Can you do it?</string>
    <string name="challenge_5">A day without TV;Spending the day without watching television will help you to do pending tasks and spend less time doing nothing.</string>
    <string name="challenge_6">Travel alone;Leave your comfort zone and dare to travel alone, without company of anyone.
        You will discover many things about yourself and learn to survive on your own without the help of anyone.</string>
    <string name="challenge_7">Life goals;Start a list with objectives in the short, medium and long term.
        The goal is not to put pressure on you, but to propose new goals and reach them little by little.</string>
    <string name="challenge_8">Go to the movies;How long have you not been to the movies?
        Look at the card and decide which movie you\'re going to watch today. Do not forget the popcorn, and of course, a good company :)!</string>
    <string name="challenge_9">Bake a cake; Usually you usually eat cakes on special occasions, however,
        this time, we suggest you bake a cake and eat a piece, for the simple pleasure of eating cake!</string>
    <string name="challenge_10">Write a letter;Today writing a letter is something very rare, so, we suggest you write a letter to someone you love.
        Yes, it must be a letter, it can not be an e-mail!</string>
    <string name="challenge_11">Healthy food;Propose for today eat as healthy as possible, it will help you feel better and who knows, maybe you get used to it! :)</string>
    <string name="challenge_12">Time with your pet;Sometimes we forget to spend time with our pet, give him love and make them happy by spending a little time with them,
        taking them to the mountain in the case of dogs ... We propose that you do something different with your pet today, make him feel special!
        If you do not have a pet, you can apply it to a relative.</string>
    <string name="challenge_13">Learn something new;How long have you not learned anything new on your own initiative?
        Today is a good time for this, think about something you do not know much about and research about it!</string>
    <string name="challenge_14">Bad habits;Do you have any bad habits? Any mania? For example, do you usually bite your nails?
        It is a good time to end any bad habit!</string>
    <string name="challenge_15">Stop smoking;Do you usually smoke? Today is a good time to leave this unhealthy "hobby" and start having a better life.
        In addition, you will also notice it in your pocket! If on the contrary you do not smoke, continue like this, you are on the right track!</string>
    <string name="challenge_16">Shopping;Remember when it was the last time you went to buy clothes for pure pleasure and not out of necessity?
        Today can be a day to remember, go to your favorite mall and buy something beautiful! :)</string>
    <string name="challenge_17">New hobby; It is always a good time to start that hobby that you always thought but for which you did not have time.
        Cook? Photography? Drawing? The choice is yours!</string>
    <string name="challenge_18">Call an old friend;Do you remember that friend you have not talked to for years?
        Maybe you could try to get back in touch. Make a call and discover what is your life now!</string>
    <string name="challenge_19">Start a blog;Relax writing about any topic you want or try to create tutorials on a topic that you master.
        The possibilities are endless and will help you have a good time and do not waste time!</string>
</resources>
